[Music]
Ajay has
installed the
phone number. In this learning video, we will
learn how to use ICICI
Lombard's two-wheeler point system. As
you can see, we are currently on the home screen.
Here, we will enter the mobile number of the customer who has come to buy a two-wheeler policy
and click on search.
You will see a message. Here, 'New
Potential Customers' is written on the right side. By
showing all this, it means that this customer is
not in our database and he is a
customer for all three payment banks.
Today, in Mumbai Diary, if
you look here, we are
shown many options below: Account Opening,
Recharge, Bill Payment, Remittance. If you
look a little here and look on the right side,
then the Insurance option is also shown.
Amit, click on the central icon. If you
look here, three options like Life, General, Health are
shown. Here, we
will click on the General option, on which
ICICI Lombard will click on the Other option. If
you look inside here,
two options like Product and Services are shown.
We will click on the Product option
and in it, we will see the To Be Our option.  We will click on it,
I will come here and click on generate code,
I will see it here, we have to follow these steps,
first enter in, then second got
third application for payment 50% 2196 summary link
of the policy, first of all in Amazon,
here see the first point in information
and similarly there is new business, here if
you click on download then there are
two options New Business and Rover, from which we will
select any one option, we will select the use option,
if the customer's vehicle
is less than one year old, that is,
if the customer comes to us for a policy within one year of buying the bike, then
we will select this business option,
now if the customer comes to renew his bike policy, then
we will select the roll option,
in the ruler option you have to keep a few things in mind,
first of all you cannot renew any existing
ICICI Lombard two wheeler policy, that is,
if the customer's bike policy
is from ICICI Lombard, then you
cannot renew it, so the customer's two
wheeler policy must be from some other company.
So suppose the customer's policy was from SBI General
Insurance and we are selecting it here,
one of the most
important things
here is that if someone had taken bike
insurance and his policy has lapsed, or
his bike service policy has
lapsed, that is, on the
day his policy expired
and within 3 months of that, he is
required to come and take the policy from us,
if three months have passed since the customer's policy expired, then
we could not wait for such type of two
wheeler,
now we have to make the vehicle manifest raw seal, all these stars that
you are seeing, that
star means that all these are mandatory in a
compulsory frill, which we will
keep black, we cannot proceed further to take the policy, before this the
vehicle
manufacturer should be there, so we will click on it, it is
here,
after clicking, as soon as you
go to type the name of the manufacturer,
you will see options in the don, so understand that
we are buying Honda motorcycle
and after that you will click on Vikram model
and you will see Vikram  If you go to write, you will see
that Juvekar Manufactured, that is the car
model, that is the
name of all of you, then it will be displayed, from that
we will take the customer's name, along with this,
in the description field you can describe it by doing the same, you
can also keep an optional Tiwari Feet plan
and after that in the RTO State field
we will
enter the state name in which we bought our car, when you
start writing it you will get a option in groups from
which we will select the state,
after this we will enter Article on Christian,
confirm that we have checked,
you will see the fitter option of IT on location
and if I
wrote Somi, then Maharashtra
came here, we took that Surya
Aditya location, we are writing it, you should carefully
see whether this RTO location is mentioned in its partial copy
or not, after this you will see, then
here you have to enter the current showroom price
which is showing 50,000 to 6 for Z1,
so we can enter the price of 6300 here,
above this range you cannot try center
Below a new range,
today we will suggest you that whatever is
shown here in hiring, you
can download it in 80 and enter it here, the train near by default will be one
year, as you can see, here there is a
date of registration, date of birth change
option, as you can see, date of birth
registration Yadav will be a wrong decision
and date of purchase, if the customer is a Fortuner
two wheeler, then date of birth registration
and date of birth change of both the teams, and
if the customer is a Halka, then the
date of birth registration will be when the vehicle was
first registered in the video and the date of birth
change will be when Bigg Boss
bought the vehicle, so here because this
first date of birth registration will be
kept from the date of birth and and the manufacturing of
Bigg Boss Chinese, here
I have to select whether you have got no claim bonus in the previous policy
or not, did
you get no claim bonus in the previous policy,
you will be taking it from here or you will
take it from there, okay, if you have
positive and comment how much no claim bonus you have got in the previous policy,
you will see that, the number which you  We have brought the
previous policy of management and no claim
bonus from here and have come from England,
now they have not received the no claim bonus, you
will select the note, your car is pavilion end, it is
badhook away policy, hence you have
taken it from here, then you will enter the start date of your previous policy
and here in the start date of your
NDA, here in the start date
you will select
that the start date of your policy is from October
2017 to
11-10-2018 MDS, if you have
taken any claim in the previous policy, then you
will select
that after that your Singh and how many times you have
cleared it, again already,
if you have not taken any claim in your previous policy, then
you will note
that your privacy policy type is
comprehensive, you will
not do it earlier, the
state and customer type will be individual,
when you select the reaction
and select RTI forum no,
in Suji state we will do the meeting here,
we have taken the car from this test, then
after entering the details you will click on it,
now
here you will see us  This is being shown. The
approximate premium is ₹100.90.
After seeing the shrink, we
will share the mp3 and with the customer and after greasing it,
click on next. Now on
this screen we will enter the customer details,
enter nominated and some other
information which has been written in partial copy, that is
why enter the customer's name,
write gender, date of birth etc.
Unique ID will have to be mentioned about this. Unique
ID is basically the Aadhar number of the customer which will have to be
maintained.
Aadhar number, internet and mobile number which
we had entered in the beginning will automatically appear here.
We will enter the address of the customer here. We will have to
enter the email ID of the customer
here. Now
this will have to be done. We will
always keep the comparison in the relation of us and our vehicle here.
A big as comprehensive package at the
time of claim not only
compensates for the loss of the other person but also the loss of your vehicle.  We will
enter the vehicle number
which is written in the RC book, so
after entering the details,
we will keep a line from the yesterday date and this
Asif, after entering these details and
after entering the details of the preventions, the
internet was available in access, we will click on Next,
now
as you can see here,
this is the final payment piece, we will
take the terms and conditions here and here
we are giving our connection in the second track, to
create a low KYC wallet in our system, Utsav and
Fourth Safe Step, after clicking on Next,
we will again go to, on
clicking the Next button, you will see the
decoration screen, here you give the customer
information and click on the Accept button,
now here you are asking the customer for authentication,
then here basically we will
place the customer's finger in this circle with the
help of which we will take finger authentication,
now as soon as you tick this circular, the
biometric device will be correct and you
can take Candy Crush to the customer through the biometric device,
a successful biometric  As soon as the authentication is done, an
OTP will come on the customer's registered number. After
taking the OTP from the customer, you enter it here.
After entering the OTP,
click on the next button.
Now you can see that as I have clicked
next here, this two-wheeler policy has been
booked through policy.
We have successfully logged in for this customer's two-wheeler policy.
Now this policy has gone to the Map Speed ​​​​of your branch
for approval. So, you get
this policy approved through Speed. As soon as it is
approved, you go to the history and
download and print the customer's CEO of your Certificate of Insurance document and
subscribe.